[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 10 + 7?",
        "options": [
            12,
            18,
            17,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 13 + 12?",
        "options": [
            26,
            21,
            30,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 18 + 11?",
        "options": [
            33,
            29,
            34,
            32
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 13 + 9?",
        "options": [
            22,
            17,
            19,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 13 + 6?",
        "options": [
            18,
            16,
            17,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 19 + 19?",
        "options": [
            40,
            37,
            33,
            38
        ],
        "answer": 38
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 6 + 9?",
        "options": [
            15,
            16,
            14,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 15 + 15?",
        "options": [
            28,
            30,
            31,
            32
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
        "options": [
            2,
            7,
            5,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 20 + 18?",
        "options": [
            40,
            35,
            38,
            33
        ],
        "answer": 38
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 10 + 11?",
        "options": [
            23,
            21,
            26,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 8 + 6?",
        "options": [
            17,
            16,
            14,
            15
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 10 + 13?",
        "options": [
            22,
            18,
            23,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 14 + 20?",
        "options": [
            29,
            34,
            37,
            32
        ],
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 17 + 19?",
        "options": [
            39,
            36,
            32,
            35
        ],
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 4 + 8?",
        "options": [
            14,
            13,
            7,
            12
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 17 + 10?",
        "options": [
            26,
            24,
            25,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 1 + 11?",
        "options": [
            12,
            13,
            8,
            15
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 14 + 18?",
        "options": [
            35,
            34,
            30,
            32
        ],
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 1 + 15?",
        "options": [
            15,
            16,
            14,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 22 + 50?",
        "options": [
            72,
            71,
            79,
            70
        ],
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 42 + 38?",
        "options": [
            80,
            74,
            87,
            86
        ],
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 45 + 23?",
        "options": [
            69,
            63,
            73,
            68
        ],
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 33 + 42?",
        "options": [
            75,
            72,
            80,
            77
        ],
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 24 + 41?",
        "options": [
            65,
            70,
            61,
            67
        ],
        "answer": 65
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 46 + 49?",
        "options": [
            101,
            95,
            91,
            99
        ],
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 26 + 47?",
        "options": [
            71,
            73,
            76,
            69
        ],
        "answer": 73
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 46 + 39?",
        "options": [
            85,
            91,
            84,
            77
        ],
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 22 + 49?",
        "options": [
            71,
            67,
            64,
            76
        ],
        "answer": 71
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 30 + 37?",
        "options": [
            65,
            66,
            67,
            63
        ],
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 33 + 37?",
        "options": [
            65,
            69,
            64,
            70
        ],
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 45 + 47?",
        "options": [
            92,
            88,
            91,
            101
        ],
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 33 + 45?",
        "options": [
            75,
            83,
            80,
            78
        ],
        "answer": 78
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 27 + 26?",
        "options": [
            53,
            49,
            51,
            50
        ],
        "answer": 53
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 34 + 35?",
        "options": [
            66,
            69,
            64,
            73
        ],
        "answer": 69
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 40 + 47?",
        "options": [
            85,
            80,
            82,
            87
        ],
        "answer": 87
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 43 + 49?",
        "options": [
            98,
            93,
            89,
            92
        ],
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 22 + 25?",
        "options": [
            42,
            47,
            44,
            48
        ],
        "answer": 47
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 24 + 29?",
        "options": [
            57,
            56,
            53,
            52
        ],
        "answer": 53
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 21 + 26?",
        "options": [
            46,
            52,
            47,
            49
        ],
        "answer": 47
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 72 + 88?",
        "options": [
            160,
            172,
            156,
            167
        ],
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 74 + 74?",
        "options": [
            157,
            150,
            146,
            148
        ],
        "answer": 148
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 68 + 62?",
        "options": [
            123,
            130,
            125,
            121
        ],
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 58 + 84?",
        "options": [
            128,
            130,
            142,
            146
        ],
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 89 + 55?",
        "options": [
            151,
            147,
            152,
            144
        ],
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 55 + 85?",
        "options": [
            140,
            153,
            139,
            126
        ],
        "answer": 140
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 53 + 88?",
        "options": [
            128,
            145,
            141,
            150
        ],
        "answer": 141
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 75 + 88?",
        "options": [
            163,
            176,
            152,
            171
        ],
        "answer": 163
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 60 + 85?",
        "options": [
            145,
            153,
            142,
            132
        ],
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 77 + 78?",
        "options": [
            160,
            155,
            158,
            167
        ],
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 98 + 100?",
        "options": [
            210,
            180,
            215,
            198
        ],
        "answer": 198
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 70 + 59?",
        "options": [
            134,
            121,
            129,
            141
        ],
        "answer": 129
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 59 + 58?",
        "options": [
            120,
            121,
            125,
            117
        ],
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 55 + 57?",
        "options": [
            118,
            114,
            123,
            112
        ],
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 62 + 59?",
        "options": [
            122,
            127,
            121,
            114
        ],
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 60 + 95?",
        "options": [
            159,
            141,
            155,
            161
        ],
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "id": 57,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 86 + 56?",
        "options": [
            128,
            156,
            149,
            142
        ],
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "id": 58,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 97 + 74?",
        "options": [
            163,
            154,
            174,
            171
        ],
        "answer": 171
    },
    {
        "id": 59,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 55 + 83?",
        "options": [
            138,
            134,
            128,
            147
        ],
        "answer": 138
    },
    {
        "id": 60,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 94 + 87?",
        "options": [
            181,
            170,
            199,
            176
        ],
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 27 - 23?",
        "options": [
            9,
            4,
            7,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 26 - 9?",
        "options": [
            20,
            16,
            22,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 21 - 2?",
        "options": [
            21,
            19,
            18,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 29 - 23?",
        "options": [
            11,
            8,
            6,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 28 - 26?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 66,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 26 - 2?",
        "options": [
            27,
            24,
            22,
            29
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "id": 67,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 17 - 6?",
        "options": [
            15,
            6,
            11,
            16
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 68,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 19 - 2?",
        "options": [
            14,
            17,
            16,
            12
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 69,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 22 - 13?",
        "options": [
            6,
            9,
            10,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 70,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 12 - 8?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            1,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 71,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 27 - 10?",
        "options": [
            22,
            17,
            19,
            12
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 72,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 21 - 12?",
        "options": [
            4,
            9,
            14,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 73,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 30 - 4?",
        "options": [
            27,
            26,
            28,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "id": 74,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 12 - 1?",
        "options": [
            8,
            11,
            13,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 75,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 30 - 7?",
        "options": [
            23,
            19,
            18,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "id": 76,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 28 - 25?",
        "options": [
            4,
            2,
            1,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 77,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 10 - 3?",
        "options": [
            6,
            9,
            7,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 78,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 20 - 8?",
        "options": [
            10,
            15,
            12,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 79,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 20 - 1?",
        "options": [
            19,
            21,
            14,
            24
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 80,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 25 - 4?",
        "options": [
            24,
            20,
            25,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 81,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 39 - 14?",
        "options": [
            21,
            26,
            25,
            28
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "id": 82,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 68 - 52?",
        "options": [
            13,
            18,
            16,
            15
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 83,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 40 - 30?",
        "options": [
            10,
            9,
            12,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 84,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 60 - 33?",
        "options": [
            24,
            22,
            27,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "id": 85,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 56 - 24?",
        "options": [
            30,
            32,
            36,
            34
        ],
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "id": 86,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 57 - 54?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            6,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 87,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 52 - 12?",
        "options": [
            35,
            40,
            42,
            39
        ],
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "id": 88,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 67 - 51?",
        "options": [
            16,
            19,
            21,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 89,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 40 - 25?",
        "options": [
            12,
            15,
            14,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 90,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 32 - 30?",
        "options": [
            1,
            4,
            2,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 91,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 53 - 37?",
        "options": [
            16,
            15,
            11,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 92,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 43 - 13?",
        "options": [
            35,
            25,
            28,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "id": 93,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 48 - 28?",
        "options": [
            17,
            20,
            16,
            23
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 94,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 42 - 40?",
        "options": [
            4,
            5,
            1,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 95,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 64 - 62?",
        "options": [
            4,
            0,
            5,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 96,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 63 - 23?",
        "options": [
            44,
            41,
            36,
            40
        ],
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "id": 97,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 34 - 10?",
        "options": [
            24,
            20,
            29,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "id": 98,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 46 - 33?",
        "options": [
            12,
            13,
            15,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "id": 99,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 58 - 41?",
        "options": [
            14,
            17,
            22,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 100,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 60 - 49?",
        "options": [
            16,
            13,
            11,
            12
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 101,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 119 - 80?",
        "options": [
            42,
            43,
            39,
            41
        ],
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "id": 102,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 77 - 66?",
        "options": [
            10,
            16,
            9,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 103,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 93 - 64?",
        "options": [
            27,
            29,
            24,
            34
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "id": 104,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 148 - 87?",
        "options": [
            61,
            62,
            56,
            58
        ],
        "answer": 61
    },
    {
        "id": 105,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 110 - 46?",
        "options": [
            64,
            63,
            58,
            67
        ],
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "id": 106,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 75 - 36?",
        "options": [
            42,
            35,
            40,
            39
        ],
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "id": 107,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 90 - 36?",
        "options": [
            54,
            50,
            57,
            59
        ],
        "answer": 54
    },
    {
        "id": 108,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 86 - 76?",
        "options": [
            14,
            12,
            10,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 109,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 78 - 56?",
        "options": [
            18,
            24,
            22,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "id": 110,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 143 - 56?",
        "options": [
            92,
            87,
            79,
            93
        ],
        "answer": 87
    },
    {
        "id": 111,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 99 - 38?",
        "options": [
            65,
            61,
            56,
            58
        ],
        "answer": 61
    },
    {
        "id": 112,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 116 - 82?",
        "options": [
            35,
            32,
            34,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "id": 113,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 72 - 48?",
        "options": [
            23,
            20,
            24,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "id": 114,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 72 - 51?",
        "options": [
            21,
            23,
            20,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 115,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 138 - 135?",
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            4,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 116,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 134 - 56?",
        "options": [
            74,
            73,
            75,
            78
        ],
        "answer": 78
    },
    {
        "id": 117,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 109 - 84?",
        "options": [
            30,
            20,
            25,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "id": 118,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 85 - 64?",
        "options": [
            25,
            21,
            24,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 119,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 133 - 44?",
        "options": [
            89,
            87,
            90,
            97
        ],
        "answer": 89
    },
    {
        "id": 120,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 129 - 86?",
        "options": [
            43,
            41,
            38,
            47
        ],
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "id": 121,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 3?",
        "options": [
            13,
            8,
            9,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 122,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 3?",
        "options": [
            12,
            19,
            15,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 123,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 6?",
        "options": [
            26,
            25,
            24,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "id": 124,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 2 \u00d7 6?",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            17,
            12
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 125,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 3?",
        "options": [
            10,
            8,
            5,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 126,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 4?",
        "options": [
            22,
            29,
            24,
            23
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "id": 127,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 5?",
        "options": [
            28,
            30,
            29,
            31
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "id": 128,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 4?",
        "options": [
            11,
            16,
            14,
            15
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 129,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 5?",
        "options": [
            20,
            22,
            15,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 130,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 3?",
        "options": [
            21,
            20,
            18,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "id": 131,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 4?",
        "options": [
            17,
            12,
            7,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 132,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 2?",
        "options": [
            13,
            7,
            10,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 133,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 2 \u00d7 6?",
        "options": [
            7,
            15,
            12,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 134,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 4?",
        "options": [
            20,
            21,
            18,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 135,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 2 \u00d7 5?",
        "options": [
            6,
            13,
            14,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 136,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 3?",
        "options": [
            8,
            5,
            4,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 137,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 3?",
        "options": [
            12,
            15,
            8,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 138,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 5?",
        "options": [
            21,
            17,
            23,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 139,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 2 \u00d7 2?",
        "options": [
            4,
            2,
            3,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 140,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 3?",
        "options": [
            22,
            13,
            16,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "id": 141,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 12?",
        "options": [
            81,
            92,
            89,
            84
        ],
        "answer": 84
    },
    {
        "id": 142,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 10?",
        "options": [
            90,
            83,
            82,
            95
        ],
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "id": 143,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 8?",
        "options": [
            56,
            51,
            61,
            57
        ],
        "answer": 56
    },
    {
        "id": 144,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 7?",
        "options": [
            58,
            59,
            54,
            56
        ],
        "answer": 56
    },
    {
        "id": 145,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 11?",
        "options": [
            125,
            128,
            132,
            144
        ],
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "id": 146,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 11?",
        "options": [
            139,
            132,
            136,
            137
        ],
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "id": 147,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 7?",
        "options": [
            59,
            57,
            63,
            65
        ],
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "id": 148,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 12?",
        "options": [
            96,
            92,
            88,
            93
        ],
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "id": 149,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 9?",
        "options": [
            78,
            79,
            72,
            69
        ],
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "id": 150,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 7?",
        "options": [
            65,
            63,
            68,
            58
        ],
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "id": 151,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 12?",
        "options": [
            83,
            84,
            87,
            76
        ],
        "answer": 84
    },
    {
        "id": 152,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 8?",
        "options": [
            79,
            66,
            72,
            65
        ],
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "id": 153,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 9?",
        "options": [
            93,
            98,
            101,
            99
        ],
        "answer": 99
    },
    {
        "id": 154,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 10?",
        "options": [
            80,
            81,
            84,
            83
        ],
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "id": 155,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 7?",
        "options": [
            63,
            64,
            70,
            75
        ],
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "id": 156,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 12?",
        "options": [
            147,
            154,
            144,
            148
        ],
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "id": 157,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 7?",
        "options": [
            71,
            75,
            77,
            70
        ],
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "id": 158,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 12?",
        "options": [
            80,
            87,
            84,
            91
        ],
        "answer": 84
    },
    {
        "id": 159,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 12?",
        "options": [
            126,
            132,
            143,
            122
        ],
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "id": 160,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 10?",
        "options": [
            104,
            110,
            112,
            106
        ],
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "id": 161,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 15 \u00d7 20?",
        "options": [
            322,
            300,
            280,
            311
        ],
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "id": 162,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 13?",
        "options": [
            264,
            235,
            247,
            258
        ],
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "id": 163,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 16?",
        "options": [
            271,
            270,
            256,
            258
        ],
        "answer": 256
    },
    {
        "id": 164,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 20?",
        "options": [
            385,
            403,
            360,
            400
        ],
        "answer": 400
    },
    {
        "id": 165,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 18?",
        "options": [
            304,
            326,
            324,
            310
        ],
        "answer": 324
    },
    {
        "id": 166,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 19?",
        "options": [
            295,
            304,
            330,
            276
        ],
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "id": 167,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 20?",
        "options": [
            318,
            312,
            340,
            357
        ],
        "answer": 340
    },
    {
        "id": 168,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 18?",
        "options": [
            268,
            274,
            288,
            275
        ],
        "answer": 288
    },
    {
        "id": 169,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 18?",
        "options": [
            274,
            301,
            309,
            288
        ],
        "answer": 288
    },
    {
        "id": 170,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 18?",
        "options": [
            268,
            231,
            252,
            276
        ],
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "id": 171,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 16?",
        "options": [
            302,
            304,
            312,
            330
        ],
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "id": 172,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 15 \u00d7 18?",
        "options": [
            277,
            270,
            281,
            255
        ],
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "id": 173,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 15 \u00d7 20?",
        "options": [
            289,
            300,
            313,
            329
        ],
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "id": 174,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 13?",
        "options": [
            261,
            262,
            260,
            259
        ],
        "answer": 260
    },
    {
        "id": 175,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 17?",
        "options": [
            251,
            232,
            231,
            238
        ],
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "id": 176,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 15?",
        "options": [
            269,
            285,
            289,
            286
        ],
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "id": 177,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 20?",
        "options": [
            355,
            360,
            371,
            365
        ],
        "answer": 360
    },
    {
        "id": 178,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 19?",
        "options": [
            285,
            317,
            304,
            287
        ],
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "id": 179,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 17?",
        "options": [
            336,
            321,
            306,
            279
        ],
        "answer": 306
    },
    {
        "id": 180,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 14?",
        "options": [
            263,
            267,
            266,
            288
        ],
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "id": 181,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 3?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            7,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 182,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 6 \u00f7 2?",
        "options": [
            5,
            3,
            4,
            7
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 183,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            5,
            3,
            6,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "id": 184,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 3?",
        "options": [
            3,
            7,
            4,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 185,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 10 \u00f7 2?",
        "options": [
            3,
            8,
            5,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 186,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 15 \u00f7 3?",
        "options": [
            2,
            9,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 187,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 4?",
        "options": [
            8,
            6,
            5,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "id": 188,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 8 \u00f7 4?",
        "options": [
            3,
            4,
            2,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 189,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 30 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            5,
            8,
            7,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 190,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 8 \u00f7 2?",
        "options": [
            6,
            5,
            1,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 191,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            8,
            6,
            10,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "id": 192,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 15 \u00f7 5?",
        "options": [
            6,
            3,
            8,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 193,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            4,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 194,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 4 \u00f7 2?",
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            5,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 195,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 2?",
        "options": [
            7,
            6,
            11,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "id": 196,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 3?",
        "options": [
            4,
            2,
            6,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 197,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            7,
            5,
            2,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 198,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 30 \u00f7 5?",
        "options": [
            10,
            7,
            1,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "id": 199,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 3?",
        "options": [
            6,
            2,
            5,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 200,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 15 \u00f7 5?",
        "options": [
            0,
            5,
            6,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 201,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 20 \u00f7 4?",
        "options": [
            2,
            5,
            1,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 202,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 35 \u00f7 5?",
        "options": [
            11,
            10,
            7,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 203,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 54 \u00f7 9?",
        "options": [
            6,
            5,
            10,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "id": 204,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 70 \u00f7 10?",
        "options": [
            6,
            9,
            7,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 205,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 70 \u00f7 7?",
        "options": [
            13,
            12,
            9,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 206,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 40 \u00f7 4?",
        "options": [
            8,
            7,
            13,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 207,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 56 \u00f7 8?",
        "options": [
            5,
            2,
            6,
            7
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 208,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 55 \u00f7 5?",
        "options": [
            14,
            15,
            11,
            12
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 209,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 18 \u00f7 2?",
        "options": [
            12,
            10,
            9,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 210,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 4?",
        "options": [
            12,
            8,
            13,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 211,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 80 \u00f7 8?",
        "options": [
            10,
            9,
            6,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 212,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            5,
            10,
            8,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 213,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 60 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            6,
            12,
            10,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 214,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 120 \u00f7 10?",
        "options": [
            14,
            10,
            12,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 215,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 4?",
        "options": [
            6,
            9,
            14,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 216,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 28 \u00f7 4?",
        "options": [
            6,
            8,
            7,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 217,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 54 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            9,
            10,
            6,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 218,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 30 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            5,
            1,
            3,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 219,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 42 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            6,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 220,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 20 \u00f7 2?",
        "options": [
            10,
            14,
            6,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 221,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 90 \u00f7 9?",
        "options": [
            12,
            6,
            5,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 222,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 102 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            13,
            17,
            21,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 223,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 96 \u00f7 8?",
        "options": [
            12,
            11,
            7,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 224,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 112 \u00f7 7?",
        "options": [
            16,
            21,
            20,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 225,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 182 \u00f7 13?",
        "options": [
            14,
            13,
            12,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 226,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 90 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            20,
            15,
            11,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 227,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 52 \u00f7 4?",
        "options": [
            10,
            13,
            16,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "id": 228,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 168 \u00f7 14?",
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            10,
            7
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 229,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 121 \u00f7 11?",
        "options": [
            12,
            15,
            11,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 230,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 130 \u00f7 13?",
        "options": [
            6,
            10,
            9,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 231,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 285 \u00f7 15?",
        "options": [
            18,
            24,
            22,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 232,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 196 \u00f7 14?",
        "options": [
            14,
            16,
            17,
            15
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 233,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 90 \u00f7 9?",
        "options": [
            11,
            13,
            10,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 234,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 190 \u00f7 10?",
        "options": [
            17,
            19,
            24,
            16
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 235,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 104 \u00f7 8?",
        "options": [
            13,
            17,
            15,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "id": 236,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 114 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            24,
            21,
            18,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 237,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 3?",
        "options": [
            16,
            9,
            12,
            7
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 238,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 180 \u00f7 9?",
        "options": [
            20,
            22,
            24,
            23
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 239,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 150 \u00f7 10?",
        "options": [
            12,
            16,
            15,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 240,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 234 \u00f7 13?",
        "options": [
            18,
            17,
            15,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 18
    }
]